What was the best financial decision that you've ever made?
Obviously investing in myself.
Probably for us, both my
partner and I at the time
when we founded the company,
the best decision wasn't really our decision,
but it kind of was, is that we, early on,
the company was growing so fast, we were profitable,
but we felt like we needed additional capital
just to expand faster.
And we sought out a venture capital firm
and we spent a lot of energy working with them
because venture capital can spend
and take a lot of attention.
It's like there's a courtship that goes on.
And in the end, they decided to pass on us
and we were kind of glad
because we were so frustrated with them and the process.
So they ended up not investing in us.